{
    "kind": "Unscramble",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP3M1L1b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentences",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "me / with / argue / Don't",
                    "answer": "Don't argue with me."
                },
                {
                    "question": "jacket / Don't / your / leave / the floor / on",
                    "answer": "Don't leave your jacket on the floor."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP3M2L8b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentence",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "visit / We / our grandparents / always / on Sundays",
                    "answer": "We always visit our grandparents on Sundays."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP3M3L14b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the question",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "me / Excuse. / get / How / I / do / bus stop / to / the / ? / ",
                    "answer": "Excuse me. How do I get to the bus stop?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP3M5L21a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the mammal quiz",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "is / What / mammal / a / ?",
                    "answer": "What is a mammal?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "types / How many / of mammals / there are / ? ",
                    "answer": "How many types of mammals there are?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "mammals / Do / a / have / backbone / ?",
                    "answer": "Do mammals have a backbone?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "does / How / breathe / mammal / a / ?",
                    "answer": "How does a mammal breathe?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What / mean / does / hot-blooded / ?",
                    "answer": "What does hot-blooded mean?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "SBP3M5L24b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the questions.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "in / Italy / Was / in / Hyacynth / November / ? ",
                    "answer": "Was Hyacynth in Italy in November?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "in / she / China / September / Was / in  / ? ",
                    "answer": "Was she in China in September? "
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}